Since my mother died, living abroad
for someone like me
with scopophobia, it is eternal anxiety.
There were so many days
when I couldn't laugh.
But then,
two years, three months and 11 days ago…
Gosh!
Who are you? What?
"Oh, maybe this is how I'll get there
where is my mother?
The moment I thought that...
It's dangerous. Be careful.
TAKADA
Hello?
…I met a person who saved my life.
Thanks to him, I started training kendo.
Physical activity
helped me get out of the hole.
Darth Vader,
or just your mother
Could you look me in the eye while talking?
Yes, only to my mother.
One sec!
There is one more person.
Wonderfully.
If there's one more person in the world,
maybe there are others too.
But I wonder
why you were able to do this.
Maybe
my instinct warned me
that he was dangerous.
I see.
What a pity. It would be nice
if he was the man of your dreams.
NO. He's definitely not my type.
Honestly? She wasn't my type.
You hit her hard enough
to get injured,
but you had no symptoms?
NO.
Absolutely none.
I've never had this happen before.
Maybe I'll call it "The Wonderful Touch."
What?
It's a miracle that with this person
everything was fine.
“Miracle” is an exaggeration.
More like a coincidence.
It probably was
one-time event.
But it's still a pity.
It would be nice if she was your type.
“Miraculous Touch”?
Sorry, when's the Rainbow Palette
will it be on sale again?
I'm so sorry.
Due to certain circumstances
sales are temporarily suspended.
Why did she disappear?
I knew it.
Is it because of the new management?
No…
Will he ever come back?
- Tell me.
- Sorry.
- Tell me that.
Are you okay?
- Sorry.
- We apologize.
- All right.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
- We're very sorry.
I'm so sorry.
All right. Don't worry.
It's not okay at all.
Which time is it?
We make them so people can eat them.
Are you listening to me?
In the production of these chocolates
we put our whole hearts into it!
We want to please a lot of people.
So stop wasting them.
ROMANTICS ANONYMOUS
EPISODE 2
YUZU Truffles
"If possible,
Can I deliver Kenji's Essence?
without personal meetings?
I'm sorry about the Rainbow Palette
has been withdrawn from sale.
"The Anonymous Chocolatier."
He won't budge, will he?
What will you say to that?
"We can't sell something
not knowing
who produced it.”
This is ridiculous!
Don't call until Mom comes back!
Please calm down.
We just met.
Who do you think you are?
She was fired because she was a problem
for Futago Sweets, right?
- We just opened.
- I'm fed up with this "we"!
-Only today.
- Enough!
I knew this would happen.
Losing our mother is a huge blow to us.
He is furious that the manager left.
He will no longer cooperate with us.
I think he misunderstood it.
- Call him.
- All right.
Kumayuzu…
“A revolutionary proprietary product
created at the Golden Fruit inn.”
He blocked our number.
This is something new.
Please.
You called for me?
As for Kumayuzu…
This is an important supplier, right?
Correct.
Chef Kenji chose President Kuma's yuzu jam
from many suppliers.
His level of cuteness
goes perfectly with our chocolate.
How are our supplies?
Since we didn't get anything today,
enough for a few days.
Thank you.
Sorry.
This is delicious.
How are they made?
The secret of our yuzu truffles
lies in the production of yuzu jam.
While making jam
characteristic bitterness of yuzu
it is softened with rock salt.
That perfect balance
brings out the sweetness of the chocolate.
- They're good, right?
- And very much so.
Enjoy your meal.
Mrs. Lee Hana.
When did you find out about this?
Oh.
I like this chocolate very much.
Really?
Take care of today's schedule.
- Replace me.
- What?
Let's go to Kumayuzu together.
I? But why?
- Manager.
- Yes?
Can Mrs. Lee Hana leave?
Yes. No problem.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Please get ready.
What? All right.
If someone is angry with you,
talk to them in person.
He prefers heart to logic.
And since his wife is Korean,
another Korean woman can tip the scales
to our advantage.
But I can't drive.
As you can see, neither do I.
Faster!
Why do I have to go?
There you are, James Dean.
So what? You look nice.
You know, I almost blushed.
- Sorry for dragging you out.
- No problem.
She's our employee.
She is Korean and works in a store.
Really?
I'm Hiro.
Annyeonghaseyo?
Gosh.
Annyeonghaseyo.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Hana.
This is my friend from high school.
I asked him to take us.
You are friends.
He's smart, he plays the piano,
he is good at everything.
We were at the kendo club.
So you've been training kendo since high school.
- Yes.
- Oh my!
Why are we going to the hot springs?
We have a little problem in the Savior.
I'll explain along the way.
I see. All right.
By the way,
your Japanese is really good.
I still have a lot to learn.
I've been here for a while...
What a boor.
All right.
What did you say?
That we should go now.
Thank you for guiding.
You asked a moment ago
why he has to go.
Classic Hiro Effect.
Why are women only nice to you?
Let's go.
Thanks.
All right.
Sorry.
Oh!
If you want.
Thank you.
I bought a lot of things.
- One sec.
- Thank you.
Please.
All right.
- And this...
- Thank you.
Do you like music, Hana?
Yes.
Do you have any?
favorite genre?
I like jazz.
Seriously?
I actually have a jazz bar
near the Savior.
Gosh! Really?
The Savior guys keep coming in there.
You come too sometime.
I would love to go to Miotłka.
We also play live there.
One sec.
Did I tell you the name of the bar?
Faster. We don't have much time.
Sorry.
Let's get in.
Bright!
KUMAYUZU HOT SPRINGS GOLDEN FRUIT 1.8 KM
In Kumayuzu yuzu jam
characteristic bitterness of yuzu
it is softened with rock salt.
That perfect balance
brings out the sweetness of the chocolate.
This is key to Savior's Yuzu Truffles.
- How does that sound?
- Pretty good.
After all, I'm smart.
And annoying.
Something in Korean again?
Are you insulting me?
No, by all means.
Bat hearing.
If all goes well, I have a request.
Yes?
Please give him your hand for me.
I can't do something because of this.
But you still have your other hand.
And by whom did I get hurt?
I'm listening?
It's a bit complicated.
Will you help him?
Yes.
Of course.
Seriously?
It's definitely here somewhere.
What?
Is that a tire?
Yuck. Holy crap!
Yes, it's a tire.
Cholera!
Do you have a spare?
Check the trunk.
Need help?
No, I can handle it.
Mrs. Lee Han!
Can you help me?
I'm listening?
Can you tie this?
Thanks.
Is it under the tools?
What? Wait.
That too, please.
- It doesn't want to open.
- What?
Cinderella has been found!
I'm coming now.
- All right.
- It's a bear logo!
Let's hurry.
I'll be fine. You go.
Thanks.
- Mrs. Lee, put your hands out.
- Hands?
And my suitcase.
Let's go.
Damn, what a mess.
Carry your own suitcase!
My bag!
Faster!
But I got scared!
Hey! NO!
Sorry.
Mrs. Hana.
Please.
Nothing!
Are you okay?
- Suitcase.
- Bright.
Are you okay?
Yes, thank you.
That's good.
- How did this happen?
- Let's go!
What?
- Mrs. Lee!
- Yes!
Thank you very much!
Take care of your car!
Good morning.
I would like to talk to President Kuma.
I'm from the Savior shop.
Oh? Didn't you meet there?
Well…
You're Korean, right?
Yes.
Correct.
Oh.
So you are Korean.
Oh my. How nice! Do you speak Korean?
I am Korean.
Really? Nice to meet you.
What brings you to my husband?
Yes.
Our store urgently needs it
your yuzu jam.
Can we talk to the president?
I see. Wait a minute.
My husband is always so busy.
Hello?
We have guests here
from one of our partners.
All right.
I see. Drive safely.
Sorry.
He'll arrive a little later.
He asked if you could wait.
Can you?
Of course.
We're happy to wait until he comes back.
Thank you. Come in.
- Sorry.
- I invite.
Good morning.
He is with us.
I see. Come in.
This way, please.
Thank you.
Please come inside.
- Sorry.
- Go ahead.
Please.
Come in.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
I'll let you know as soon as my husband returns.
- Thank you.
- Make yourself comfortable.
Maybe I'll wait in the car
since it's none of my business.
No, stay. It would be awkward
if we were left alone.
I'll wait in the car.
The lady has her job here.
Sorry, I have to wash my hands.
Well, I'll go for a walk then.
Sorry.
Please.
Once upon a time,
when Chief Kenji was still alive,
he asked me for a favor.
It was
quite a strange request actually.
Request?
Yes.
It was something like that
surprise gift.
He wanted to set me up with someone.
But I was a little late
and I didn't recognize this person.
It's not because I'm late.
You shouldn't feel bad
because of such a trivial thing.
Your boss would scold you if he heard that.
He was a really nice person.
-Did you know Kenji personally?
- Oh!
Everyone said that about him.
I see.
That's true.
Yes.
He was very nice.
I knew you were nice too.
- What?
Yes?
I have something to tell you.
All right.
I…
Yes?
So…
I always liked…
I'm sorry.
YOU BETTER DON'T ANSWER
Hello?
What is this?
It's just water!
- What?
- I won't drink it!
Sorry.
What did you say?
I wanted to say…
That you like something?
Rock music!
- Rock?
- I like rock, not jazz.
- Rock.
-I'm sorry again!
Someone's calling again.
- Sorry.
- All right.
- I'm fine!
- All right?
Can you get up?
- Hello?
- I can't!
- Sorry.
- Hello?
- Are you okay?
- Let's have a drink!
Hello?
Is this Mr. Never Call?
I'm in the Miotełka bar now.
Friend…
Bartender?
You better not tell him
I said I wanted to see him.
He says not to talk
that he wants to see you.
I see.
Okay, I'm back now.
All right.
Sorry I'm leaving early.
Nothing happened.
Thank you for your help.
I owe you a debt.
All right.
Well, I'm going.
See you soon, Hana.
- Look after yourself.
- Yes.
See you.
THEREFORE, I REGARD TO INFORM YOU,
THAT WE CANNOT KEEP THIS AGREEMENT IN EFFECT
Okay!
He's going down a bit.
Welcome back!
I'm sorry you had to wait.
My husband is back!
All right.
Are you the new president of the Savior?
From Futago Sweets?
It's you, right?
Yes.
You waited so long even without a meal?
Follow me.
Please. This way.
In Kumayuzu jam
the characteristic bitterness of yuzu is…
Soothed with rock salt.
Right! Rock salt…
I'm so sorry! Please forgive me!
You drove all this way because of me!
I went to my mother,
and she scolded me
for not delivering the jam.
She's scary when she's mad.
The truth is
that when I heard that Mom had passed away,
I thought it was the arrogant new president
from Sweets Futago forced her to leave.
I couldn't forgive this.
But I was wrong.
She told me herself.
It's because of the eyes, right?
Diabetic retinopathy.
The disease progresses, right?
She said she was going home to Nagano
to focus on treatment.
You paid your pension and medical expenses.
And even introduced it to a specialist
from the university hospital.
You really went above and beyond for her.
I am grateful with all my heart!
No, I…
I didn't do anything special.
Every company would…
No!
Most people wouldn't care.
Oh no.
What?
Yes?
A shirt in your suitcase?
What?
Excuse me for a moment.
What's going on?
I have the shirt you asked for.
Gosh!
Why are you half naked?
-It's not the one.
- You wanted a clean shirt.
- This one isn't clean.
- They look the same.
That's why I ordered the whole suitcase to be brought.
Please bring it!
What a freak.
What should I do?
There's no time. Please put this on.
I can't!
Why do you have to change your clothes now?
Because…
- I told you it was complicated.
- I don't know why.
What should I do?
I don't have to explain myself to you.
- I don't want to hear it anyway.
- Enough!
I'm done.
I can't wear it.
Complete lack of manners!
He'll be back soon, so please wait.
All right.
What happened?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kuma.
You're welcome.
I stained my shirt.
That's all?
I was so worried
that I did something to upset you.
Of course not.
We recently refreshed the water.
Maybe you'll take a dip
and relax after dinner?
Are you serious?
Yes.
I want to tell you what I feel
But when you're close
I can't say a word
I really hate this about myself
I have to be brave
So as not to regret anything
I will slowly get closer to you
- And then...
- Mrs. Lee?
What song is this?
Korean?
Pretty.
What's the title?
It's a secret.
Sorry to interrupt.
Please keep singing.
And how could I?
Why…
you didn't tell me?
What?
And about what?
Why Mom left.
There were various rumors circulating.
Because…
I don't want anyone to worry about me.
Can you…
not reveal it?
Please.
All right.
RESIGNATION
She said she didn't want to
for anyone to know the real reason.
Is it really that important?
But ultimately
You kept the secret, didn't you?
He definitely appreciates it.
Is that what you think?
I'm the same.
We all have secrets.
Things we'd rather hide
or, if possible…
things no one talks about
he shouldn't find out.
Do you have such a secret?
Never mind.
You don't have to answer.
If only it were easy to say
it wouldn't be a secret.
Yes.
Dear Anonymous Chocolatier,
I changed my mind.
I want everything to stay as it is.
Please deliver chocolates as usual.
I understand you may have reasons
that you don't want to reveal.
I acted carelessly.
I would like to bring back the Rainbow Palette.
Which is why
please resume deliveries from tomorrow.
What?
From tomorrow?
What happened?
Are you okay?
No, everything's fine.
Gosh!
Once again…
Thank you very much!
- Thank you.
All right.
We'll go now.
- Good luck.
- Have a safe journey.
Take care of yourselves.
Thank you.
I invite you again.
All right.
Can I sit in the front?
Yes, please.
One sec.
Can you wrap this around your shoes?
I'm listening?
I don't want you to sit in these shoes.
Please.
All right.
What an idiot.
Sure.
What is this urgent matter at this late hour?
It's your fault, you bastard.
Another insult? Please stop.
NO. You're thinking wrong.
By the way,
I wrote to Chocolatier Anonymous.
Yes?
Since the Rainbow Palette returns tomorrow
for sale and it's the weekend,
many customers probably
can't wait.
That's why I doubled my order.
Isn't that a good idea?
Yes.
Damn, what's the deal with this ssagaji?
You were supposed to stop insulting me.
Whatever.
I said you were there
an absolute genius.
- Yes.
- Lie. Certainly not this.
- What was that? Ssagaji?
- What?
-Ssagaji?
I didn't say that.
What?
I told you you were a genius.
Can I ask something?
Why are you avoiding eye contact?
This…
my secret.
I see.
So
why can you look into my eyes?
This way.
Don't go.
Stay with me.
Just like back then.
I'll get off here.
What? Are you in a hurry?
I'll take you home.
No need.
All right.
Wait a minute.
Is…
Can I…
shake your hand?
What?
Well, because…
To thank you for everything.
All right. I have nothing against.
Thank you…
very…
for everything.
What?
One sec. Are you crying?
What? NO! Why would I cry?
You squeezed my hand too tightly.
What extraordinary strength.
I thought you were going to hurt me again.
Gosh.
I didn't know
that tears can come so suddenly.
I've never seen this before.
No exaggeration.
Now you're falling apart.
Well, sir
the first one looked sad.
You don't have to be sad with me.
It's also something new for me.
Anyway…
I'm going home.
Maybe he's not such a bad guy?
So warm.
Subtitles: Grzegorz Marczyk